<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" ?>

<Conversation>

  <Statements>
    <Statement ID="1">Hi. This is the dialog demo.</Statement>

    <Statement ID="2">What is that?</Statement>
    <Statement ID="3">I already know about this.</Statement>
    <Statement ID="4">Who cares? [Rude]</Statement>

    <Statement ID="5">The demo showcases fully data driven conversation! How are you liking it so far?</Statement>
    <Statement ID="6">Oh you do? Are you just here because you like talking? Well what do you think about it? [Friendly]</Statement>
    <Statement ID="7">Wow, you are abrasive! This is what I get for trying? [Agitated]</Statement>

    <Statement ID="8">It's alright.</Statement>
    <Statement ID="9">I want to use it in my project!</Statement>
    <Statement ID="10">It sucks hardcore! [Rude]</Statement>

    <Statement ID="11">Glad you like it!</Statement>
    <Statement ID="12">I know! You can find it at <![CDATA[https://github.com/caseydedore/DialogEngine]]></Statement>

    <Statement ID="13">Anyway... The demo showcases a fully data driven conversation system. Do you even care?</Statement>

    <Statement ID="14">I want to go shooting space pirate nazis like a decent piece of software would let me. [Rude]</Statement>

    <Statement ID="15">Let's end this. I hope I never talk to you again! [Angry]</Statement>
    <Statement ID="16">The demo is here if you want another look. Goodbye.</Statement>

    <Statement ID="17">Seriously?!?</Statement>

    <Statement ID="18">What is really cool is how the Engine can track user specified values that need to persist for the conversation.</Statement>
    <Statement ID="19">The Engine can track user specified values that need to persist for the duration of the conversation.</Statement>
    <Statement ID="20">You're really a jerkass, you know that? Made me mad... thats only partially thanks to you. The rest is thanks to the Engine.</Statement>
    
    <Statement ID="21">The engine can track values, such as my mood. Yea. Angry.</Statement>

    <Statement ID="22">These values are entirely unknown to the Engine until the user adds one. They can be modified based on the events of the conversation, and used to determine conversation flow.</Statement>

    <Statement ID="23">You're the best, Dialog Engine!</Statement>
    <Statement ID="24">Interesting.</Statement>
    <Statement ID="25">Ok. Boring.</Statement>
    <Statement ID="25">Yuck! Get me OUT OF HERE!</Statement>
    
  </Statements>

</Conversation>